[
 {
   "No": 1,
   "Quiz question": "What color is the French wine Beaujolais?",
   "Answer": "Red color"
 },
 {
   "No": 2,
   "Quiz question": "What should you do in the Arab countries to show that the food was delicious?",
   "Answer": "Belch"
 },
 {
   "No": 3,
   "Quiz question": "Which nuts are used in marzipan?",
   "Answer": "Almonds"
 },
 {
   "No": 4,
   "Quiz question": "From which cactus is tequila made?",
   "Answer": "Agave"
 },
 {
   "No": 5,
   "Quiz question": "From which country does pitta bread originate?",
   "Answer": "Greece"
 },
 {
   "No": 6,
   "Quiz question": "Which country is the origin of the cocktail Mojito?",
   "Answer": "Cuba"
 },
 {
   "No": 7,
   "Quiz question": "How many calories does a glass of water contain?",
   "Answer": "Zero calories"
 },
 {
   "No": 8,
   "Quiz question": "What is the well known drink from Greece?",
   "Answer": "Ouzo"
 },
 {
   "No": 9,
   "Quiz question": "What is called a meal in open air?",
   "Answer": "Picnic"
 },
 {
   "No": 10,
   "Quiz question": "Which cheese is traditionally used for pizzas?",
   "Answer": "Mozzarella"
 },
 {
   "No": 11,
   "Quiz question": "Which country is the origin of the Stella beer?",
   "Answer": "Belgium"
 },
 {
   "No": 12,
   "Quiz question": "From which country is the famous Emmental Cheese?",
   "Answer": "Switzerland"
 },
 {
   "No": 13,
   "Quiz question": "What is the most famous Mexican beer?",
   "Answer": "Corona"
 },
 {
   "No": 14,
   "Quiz question": "What is the name of the gas that let rise bread dough?",
   "Answer": "Carbon dioxide"
 },
 {
   "No": 15,
   "Quiz question": "What is Japanese sake made from?",
   "Answer": "Rice"
 },
 {
   "No": 16,
   "Quiz question": "What is bottled a lot in the French town Vichy?",
   "Answer": "Water"
 },
 {
   "No": 17,
   "Quiz question": "Which French town is known for its mustard?",
   "Answer": "Dijon"
 },
 {
   "No": 18,
   "Quiz question": "What is the chemical formula for Table Salt?",
   "Answer": "NaCl"
 },
 {
   "No": 19,
   "Quiz question": "What beer is marketed as The king of beers?",
   "Answer": "Budweiser"
 },
 {
   "No": 20,
   "Quiz question": "What is the name of the pan in which one makes paella?",
   "Answer": "Paella (Paella means pan)"
 },
 {
   "No": 21,
   "Quiz question": "With which fruit is Kriek beer (a Belgium brew) is flavoured?",
   "Answer": "Cherries"
 },
 {
   "No": 22,
   "Quiz question": "What is the real meaning of the Greek word Pita?",
   "Answer": "Bread"
 },
 {
   "No": 23,
   "Quiz question": "What is the Hungarian word for pepper?",
   "Answer": "Paprika"
 },
 {
   "No": 24,
   "Quiz question": "What is a banana called in Malaysia?",
   "Answer": "Pisang"
 },
 {
   "No": 25,
   "Quiz question": "What is the most famous beer in Ireland?",
   "Answer": "Guiness"
 },
 {
   "No": 26,
   "Quiz question": "What kind of food is Manchego from Spain?",
   "Answer": "Cheese"
 },
 {
   "No": 27,
   "Quiz question": "Which country does the Peroni beer come from?",
   "Answer": "Italy"
 },
 {
   "No": 28,
   "Quiz question": "Which famous brewer from Amsterdam did die in the year 2002?",
   "Answer": "Heineken"
 },
 {
   "No": 29,
   "Quiz question": "Which vitamin is the only one that you will not find in an egg?",
   "Answer": "Vitamin C"
 }
]